we can pull them right out of that transaction receipt object
我们可以通过以下操作来把它们从 `transactionReceipt` 对象中提取出来
by typing const. Yes, used comma effective gas price equals transaction receipt.
`const  = transactionReceipt`
So again, with this curly bracket syntax,
再强调一下这里的花括号语法
we can use this to pull out objects out of another object.
我们可以用它来把一些对象从另一个对象中提取出来
And now that we have these two objects,
现在我们有了这两个对象
we can create a const gas cost or total gas cost
就可以创建 `const gasCost` 或者说总的 "gasCost"
is going to be equal to the gas used times the effective gas price.
` = gasUsed * effectiveGasPrice`
Which again, since these are both big numbers,
这里再次因为它们都是 "BigNumber"
we can use a big number function called dot mol to multiply them together.
所以我们可以用 "BigNumber" 的函数 `.mul` 来把它们乘到一起
Now that we have this total gas cost, we can come down
现在我们有了这个总的 "gasCost" 就可以拉到底下
and we can say the ending deployer balance plus that gas cost to string.
并写上 `endingDeployerBalance.add(gasCost).toString()`
Now the two of these should be equivalent.
现在这二者应该是相等的了
I know there's a lot of math that we're doing in this section and a lot of new things.
我知道这一部分我们用到了许多数学的东西以及其他一些新内容
So I want to just quickly rego over what we just learned.
所以我来快速回顾一下我们这会儿学到的东西
So first off, the font of the contract comes with a provider,
首先 "fundMe" 合约带有一个 "provider"
we could have also done ethers dot provider dot get balance,
我们也可以写成是 `ethers.provider.getBalance`
but we're using fun v dot provider because we're using the provider of the Funmi contract.
但我们要使用 `fundMe.provider` 因为我们正在使用的是 "fundMe" 合约的 `provider`
It doesn't really matter what we use here.
我们在这里使用什么其实并不重要
We just wanted to use this get balanced function of the provider object
我们只是想用 `provider` 对象的这个 `getBalance` 函数
which gets us the balance of any contract.
它可以为我们提供任意合约的资金余额
We do the same thing with starting deplore balance.
我们对 `startingDeployerBalance` 做了相同的事
The reason that we needed the starting balances
我们需要初始余额的原因
is because we wanted to compare it to the ending balances
是因为我们想要将其与最终余额进行对比
to see if all the money went to the right places,
以查看所有的钱是不是都流到了正确的地方
we then call the withdrawal function.
我们接着调用了 `withdraw` 函数
And from the transaction receipt, we grabbed the gas used and the gas price.
并从 `transactionReceipt` 中获取了 `gasUsed` 和 `gasPrice`
If you want to debug your JavaScript code, you can add a breakpoint like so
如果你想要调试你的 JavaScript 代码，可以添加一个断点，就像这样
go to run into bug, open your debug JavaScript terminal,
前往“运行和调试”，打开你的 “JavaScript 调试终端”
which is different from your regular bash terminals.
它和你常规的 bash 终端是不同的
And when you run JavaScript commands in here,
如果你在这里运行 JavaScript 命令
they will stop where your breakpoints are.
它们就会在你的断点处停止
Then you can read the different variables and see where different things are.
接着你就可以读取不同的变量，并查看它们的不同情况
Using that knowledge. We pulled out the gas use and effective gas price from the transaction receipt
使用这个知识点，我们在 "transactionReceipt" 中提取了 "gasUsed" 和 "effectiveGasPrice"
and used it to get the total gas cost of this transaction,
并使用它们获得了该交易总的 "gasCost"
we then got the ending fund, we balanced the
我们获取了 `endingFundMeBalance` 还有 `endingFundMeBalance` ending deployer balance,
and used all those variables to make sure all the money went to the right places.
并动用了全部这些变量确保了所有资金都流向了正确的地方
And we, we can check this
我们可以检查一下
by running yarn Hardhead test dash dash grep
运行 `yarn hardhat test --grep`
withdraw eath in quotes, since there's a space here,
把 "Withdraw ETH" 放到引号内，因为这里有个空格
and we can see that our test does indeed pass. Great job.
可以看到我们的测试确实通过了，干得漂亮
If we didn't add the gas cost here, and we just did.to string,
如果我们不在这里添加 "gasCost"，只是执行 `.toString()`
we would see something like this,
就会看到这样的情况
we would see that the numbers are ever so slightly off,
我们看到这些数字有一些偏差
because we're not anticipating we're not calculating the gas here.
因为我们没有预料到，没有计算上这里的 gas
So we always want to make sure we're using the gas if we're doing calculations like this.
所以我们总是要确保我们考虑了 gas，如果我们执行了类似这样的计算的话